<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.cbilling.iptv" name="Cbilling.TV IPTV" version="2.1.0" provider-name="HiDiv">
   <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource"  provides="video" library="default.py"><provides>video</provides></extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="login" />
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="resources/lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary>Cbilling.tv IPTV player</summary>
      <description>Providing access to Cbilling.TV IPTV channels and VoD. Compatible with Kodi 19+ (Matrix and later)</description>
      <disclaimer lang="en">This addon is provided "as is" without any warranty. The authors are not liable for any data loss, corruption, or damages. This addon does not host any media content; users are responsible for legal compliance in their jurisdiction.</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="ru">Аддон предоставляется «как есть» без каких-либо гарантий. Авторы не несут ответственности за потерю данных, их повреждение или любой ущерб. Аддон не размещает медиаконтент; пользователи несут ответственность за соблюдение законодательства в своей юрисдикции.</disclaimer>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <license>AGPL-3.0-only</license>
      <news>

2.1.0 (unreleased)
[fix] VOD search pagination: page parameter now passed to /filter/by_name and /filter/year API

2.0.5-dev
[fix] EPG timezone: time now displays in user's configured timezone (stb_timezone setting)
[fix] EPG time from API 'date' field (server timezone) is now ignored, Unix timestamps used instead
[fix] EPG cache: t_time/t_time_to recalculated from timestamps on read (timezone change works instantly)
[fix] SQLite: "no such table: config" crash when config table lost from existing EPG database
[fix] SQLite: "NoneType is not callable" race condition between cron and UI threads
[fix] SQLite: all connections use timeout=10 and WAL mode for concurrent access
[info] Uses dateutil.tz from vendor for timezone conversion (no new dependencies)
[info] Warning logged once if timezone setting is empty or invalid (fallback to system time)
[new] Watch history: episodes navigate to episode list instead of direct playback
[new] Episode list auto-positions cursor on the watched episode

2.0.4-dev
[new] Watch History feature for VOD (configurable size, default 5 items)
[new] Context menu for history items (remove, clear all)
[new] Settings for history management
[fix] IPTV channel sorting now respects server order
[fix] VOD pagination - now showing all items with "Next page" button
[fix] "All genres" folder now displays content correctly
[fix] urllib3 compatibility with Python 3.8 (Kodi 19.4)
[info] Added client-side pagination (20 items per page)
[info] Auto-generate episode/season names when missing

2.0.3-dev
[fix] EPG cache performance optimization
[fix] Removed blocking EPG reload on channel list open
[info] EPG now loads instantly, cache updates in background

2.0.2-dev
[fix] Python 3.8 compatibility (Kodi 19/20)
[fix] Fixed urllib3 type hints for older Python versions
[info] Tested with Kodi 19.4 (Matrix) and Kodi 20 (Nexus)

2.0.1-dev
[dev] Development version - API migration testing
[info] This is a pre-release version for testing purposes

2.0.0
[new] Migrated from Stalker Portal to new REST API
[new] Direct stream URLs (no more create_link calls)
[new] Local favorites storage (no server dependency)
[new] Simplified auth with public key
[fix] Removed dependency on mag-aura.com Stalker Portal

XX.3.0
[fix] Speed optimization
[fix] VOD opening (added to the favorites) after token expiration

XX.2.7
[fix] Improve auth error messaging

1X.2.6
[fix] Fix API server URL

1X.2.5
[fix] EPG timeout issue
[new] Add response timeout selection to the config
[new] Add stream server selection to the context menu

      </news>
      <forum>https://clck.ru/KcXML</forum>
      <assets>
         <icon>icon.png</icon>
         <fanart>fanart/archive_01.jpg</fanart>
      </assets>
   </extension>
</addon>
